**Privacy Notice**
------------------

_**Last Modified:** April 16th, 2026_

NOTE: This Privacy Notice is drafted in English. If this Privacy Notice is offered in any language other than English, it shall be for information purposes only and, in case of conflict between the English-language version and any translation thereof, the English-language version will prevail.

Introduction
------------

Aylo Freesites Ltd (hereinafter “**we**”, “**us**” or “**our**”) operates the website [https://www.youporn.com/](https://www.youporn.com/) (hereinafter "**Youporn**") and is the controller of the information collected or provided via  Youporn.

Please read this Privacy Notice carefully, as your access to and use of Youporn signifies that you have read, understood, the terms set forth in this Privacy Notice. This Privacy Notice explains how we collect, use and disclose information from individuals who visit Youporn . We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal data.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please see the Section “_Contact Information_” below for information on how to contact us.

 1. Scope
---------

For the purposes of this Privacy Notice, “**process**”, “**processed**” or “**processing**” means any operation or set of operations performed on personal data or on sets of personal data (excluding disclosure thereof), whether by automated means, including one or several of the following operations: collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction. Information on disclosure of personal data or of sets of personal data may be found in the “_Disclosure of Your Personal Information_” section below.

This Privacy Notice applies to information we collect:

*   on Youporn
*   and your communications with Youporn via email, online support chats, phoneline support or otherwise;

 2. Our Policy Towards Minors
-----------------------------

Youporn prohibits minors from using the platform. Youporn is forbidden for persons under the age of 18 and the applicable age of majority in the jurisdiction from which \[website\] is accessed. As indicated throughout this Privacy Notice, some users may be asked to provide some information to us and our service providers for us to make sure that you are over the age of majority required to have access to the \[website\] . We do not intend to process minors’ Personal Data (as defined under section 3 below). However, we and/or our service providers, could incidentally process Personal Data related to minors when carrying out our age verification process, in strict accordance with the locally applicable legal obligations which Youporn is subject to (for more details regarding the type of Personal Data processed in this context, refer to section 3 below “Identifiers”). If you are the parent or legal guardian of a minor who has provided us with personal information, then please contact us at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) to have that minor’s personal information deleted.

3\. The Data We Process About You
---------------------------------

**“Personal Data” or “Personal Information”** refers to any information relating to an individual that can be used to identify that person, either directly or indirectly or as otherwise defined by applicable law. This does not include data that has been anonymized or aggregated in such a way that the individual is no longer identifiable.

We may process different types of Personal Data about you, depending on whether you choose to create an account with us.

**Unregistered Users**

Individuals who visit Youporn without logging in or creating an account. We process the following categories of information:

*   **Contact Data:** We will only process your email address or any other information which you voluntarily provide to us at your direction for a specific function, namely, to participate in a contest or survey.
    
*   **Online Forms and Communication Data:** We process Contact Data and other information that you submit through online forms provided on Youporn or information send to us via email, online support chats or such as information provided in the context of support requests or any other inquiries, the content reporting and moderation of content, and our internal complaint handling system.
    
*   **Website activity data:** We process information about how you use Youporn and interact with content and advertisements, including the pages you visit on and search history on Youporn, and the referring web page from which you arrived on Youporn from. We process browser and operating system information, devices you use to access Youporn and your time zone setting. We also process online identifiers. Specifically, we process internet protocol (IP) address information and we set cookies as explained below in the section on _Cookies and Automatic Data Collection Technologies_.
    
*   **Identifiers:** Some users may be asked to provide identifiers (including government-issued photo identification as well as other documentation) to verify that they are over the age of majority required to have access to Youporn and to view the content. In such cases, this information is processed by trusted third party age verification service providers. This Privacy Notice does not apply to the privacy practices of these third-party age verification service providers. Read the privacy terms and conditions of these third-party service providers carefully.

**Registered Users**

Individuals who choose to create an account on Youporn will have the same categories of information processed as described above for Unregistered Users. In addition, we process the following information specifically for Registered Users:

*   **Contact Information:** We process usernames and email addresses. If you choose to register through a third-party platform, we will collect certain personal information from those platforms.
    
*   **User Submitted Personal Information:** We process information you submit to personalize your account or for a specific function, for example your date of birth, age, gender, your interests, preferences, feedback, survey responses, your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties, and your communication preferences, as well as any other information which you voluntarily provide to us at your direction for a specific function.
    
*   **Identifiers and Biometric Information:** **:** If you choose to register as a Registered User on Youporn, or if this is required for age verification purposes, we process the identifiers you submit to us (including government-issued photo identification and other documentation) to verify your age and/or identity, as well as to conduct record checks. Additionally, and if applicable in your jurisdiction, our third-party service provider will process face recognition data, which is considered biometric information, to verify your age. See the section “Biometric Information” for more details.
    
*   **User Contributions including Audio/Video Information:** We provide areas on Youporn where you can post information about yourself and others, communicate with others, upload content (e.g., pictures, video files, etc.), and post comments or reviews of content found on Youporn .

Please use caution in providing user contributions. **By providing user contributions you are making that content and information publicly available.** User contributions can be read, collected, used, and disclosed by others, and we cannot control who accesses your user contributions or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post or submit. User contributions are governed by the Youporn Terms of Service found at [/info/terms](https://www.youporn.com/info/terms).

4\. The Sources from Which We Process Personal Information
----------------------------------------------------------

We process Personal Information in the following ways:

*   **Directly from you:** We process the categories of information listed above directly from you.
    
*   **Automated technologies or interactions:** As explained in the section below on _Cookies and Automatic Data Collection Technologies_, we set cookies and other automatic techniques to process website activity data when you visit Youporn.
    
*   **Third-Party Single Sign-on:** We may obtain information if you create or sign-in your account through a third-party platform (such as Google), we will have access to certain information from that platform such as your name, email address or such other information you may have submitted and allowed this third party to share.

5\. Purposes for Which We Process Your Personal Information
-----------------------------------------------------------

We process personal information for the purposes described below.

*   **Provision of services:** We process identifiers, website activity data, contact data (if voluntarily submitted as described hereinabove) and, additionally for Registered Users only, Personal Information and user contributions, including to any interactive features on Youporn, to provide products or services that you request from us.
    
*   **Customer management and quality assurance (Registered Users Only):** We process identifiers and Contact Data to manage Registered Users’ account, to provide customer support and notices to the Registered Users about their account, and to provide notices about changes to Youporn  or any products or services we offer or provide. Additionally, we may process communications data and online forms data for training our customer support teams, quality assurance purposes, and to improve the quality of our customer service interactions.
    
*   **Age and Identity verification:** In some cases, we process identifiers (including government-issued identification that may be considered sensitive data) and will use third party service providers to process sensitive data, including biometric information for the purpose of verifying your identity and the authenticity of the identifiers you provide to us while registering for an account on Youporn.
    
*   **Customization of content and marketing (Unregistered Users and Registered Users):** We process for both Registered Users and Unregistered Users, identifiers and contact information, website activity data; and for Registered Users, user submitted personal information and user contributions to analyze your use of, or interest in, the content, products, or services, to develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests on Youporn.
    
*   **Communications and handling of requests:** We process Online Forms and Communications Data and other information as necessary to respond to and resolve any of your requests, including where this is required to ensure compliance with our legal obligations.
    
*   **Analytics:** We process identifiers and website activity data to determine whether users of Youporn are unique, or whether the same user is using Youporn on multiple occasions, and to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, demographic patterns.
    
*   **Product improvement:** We may process activity data, user submitted Personal Information, and user contributions to improve our products and services. 
    
*   **Functionality and security:** We may process any of the categories of data we process to diagnose or fix technology problems, and to detect, prevent, and respond to actual or potential fraud, illegal activities, or intellectual property infringement.
    
*   **Fraud Prevention and Risk Management:** We may process any of the categories of Personal Data mentioned herein to diagnose or fix technology problems, to detect, prevent, and respond to actual or potential fraudulent, illegal activities, unauthorized access, identity theft, or intellectual property infringement. This includes monitoring unusual patterns of behaviour, maintaining security of accounts, user authentication and transactions. 
    
*   **Platform safety**: We may process any of the categories of Personal Data mentioned herein to promote safety and security on Youporn . We use the information we collect to help protect Youporn users from harm and provide safe, secure product.
    
*   **Compliance:** We may process any of the categories of data we process to enforce our Terms of Service and to comply with our legal obligations. In certain jurisdictions, this includes our legal obligation to verify the age of users having access to Youporn.
    
*   **Hash Values:** We may create hash values from any of the categories of data we process, such as infringing or illegal content to train our models to detect, prevent, and combat illegal activities including fraud, sexual assault, or exploitation. We reserve the right to share any hashes with law enforcement agencies.
    
*   **Business Operations and Administration:** We may process contact data, identifiers, transaction data, and website activity data for internal business administration purposes, including accounting, auditing, recordkeeping, insurance purposes, corporate governance, reporting, and business planning.
    
*   **Legal Defence:** We may process any of the categories of Personal Data mentioned herein to establish, exercise, or defend our legal rights in connection with actual or potential legal proceedings, disputes, or claims. This includes disclosing Personal Data to our legal counsel, courts, and other parties involved in legal proceedings where necessary to protect our interests or comply with legal processes.
    
*   **Business Transfers and Corporate Transactions:** We may process any categories of Personal Data in connection with potential or actual mergers, acquisitions, divestitures, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding.
    
*   **Information you provide:** We will process contact information and user submitted personal information in any other way we may describe when you provide the information; or for any other purpose with your consent provided separately from this Privacy Notice.

6\. Our Legal Bases Under Canadian and European Union (EU) Privacy Law
----------------------------------------------------------------------

To the extent required by applicable law, we rely on several lawful bases to use your data in these ways. This means we process your personal data only where:

*   You provide your consent to do so for a specific purpose: for example, when you allow us to show you personalized ads or to send you e-mail marketing.
    
*   Biometric information may in some instances also be processed by our third-party service provider based on your consent for identification and age verification purposes. You may withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any collection, use, processing, or disclosure that occurred prior to the withdrawal.
    
*   It is necessary to perform our contract with you: for example, to create your account and provide our services.
    
*   It is necessary to comply with our legal obligations: for example, we may be required to collect, use, or disclose your information in connection with civil, criminal, corporate, taxation, regulatory matters, or litigation.
    
*   It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests): for example, to keep Youporn safe and secure from fraud and illegal activities.
    
*   It is used to protect your or others’ vital interests: for example, in case of emergency or to prevent a crime or fraud.
    
*   It is used for tasks carried out in the public interest: for example, to combat unlawful behaviour where it is in the public interest to do so and where the public interest is laid down by applicable law.

Depending on the circumstances, we may rely on different legal bases when processing your same information for different purposes. If you reside outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), Switzerland or the United Kingdom (“UK”), the legal bases on which we rely may differ from those listed above.

7\. Disclosure of Your Personal Information
-------------------------------------------

We disclose your Personal Information when necessary to perform the services or for other purposes set out in this Privacy Notice. Disclosure of your Personal Information may also involve transfers of your Personal Information outside the your country of residence. To the extent that you reside in the EEA and the UK and where we need to transfer Personal Information outside the EEA, we will do so according to the section “_Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries_” or when necessary for the performance of the contract between us. The parties to whom we may disclose your Personal Information include: 

*   **The public:** When you submit user contributions including audio/video content, you are using Youporn and services to make that information public.
*   **Our contractors:** To provide our services to you, our contractors may receive access to your Personal Data only on a need-to-know basis. Such contractors abide by confidentiality obligations. 
*   **Our corporate group:** We may disclose any of the categories of Personal Information that we collect to members of our corporate group  to the extent this is necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice, and generally to operate our business, which includes: identification and age verification purposes, transaction monitoring and payment processing, customer support, facilitating business and product development (including for AI product improvement), administering user accounts or providing IT, technical and engineering support. You acknowledge that in some cases, members of our corporate group might be established or run their services outside the EEA.  
*   **Linked Third-Party Websites or Single Sign-On (SSO) Services**: You may choose to sign-in, connect or register an account using an external third-party platform, or Single Sign-On (SSO) if available. If you choose to connect your account to a third-party platform, the providers of this platform may receive information about you. When you use third-party platforms, their own terms and privacy policies will govern their use. 
    
*   **Service providers:** We disclose certain categories of Personal Information to our authorized service providers (such as identity and age verification providers; hosting, infrastructure and content delivery providers; IT maintenance, performance monitoring and security providers; analytics and user experience providers; communication and email service providers; customer service and support platforms; )to enable us to provide our services to you pursuant to our Terms & Conditions. These service providers may use your information only to perform these tasks on our behalf, such as identity and document authenticity verification including biometric processing, age verification, risk and fraud detection and mitigation, customer service, marketing and advertising, customization of content, analytics, security, hosting or supporting Youporn ’s functionality. These service providers have limited access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to process such information for any other purposes. You can [view the list of our third-party service providers acting as our processors](https://www.youporn.com/information/processors/).
    
*   **Legal successors:** We may disclose the categories of personal information we process to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, acquisition or sale or transfer of some or all our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding. Such transactions may be in our legitimate interest, particularly our interest in making decisions that enable our business to develop.
    
*   **To comply with the law or protect our rights or the rights of third parties:** We access, preserve and share all of the categories of personal information with regulators, law enforcement or others where we reasonably believe such disclosure is needed to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, this also includes our Trust and Safety initiative, in the scope of which we may disclose some information to several recipients, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address illegal or suspected illegal activities, security, or technical issues, (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; or (e) to maintain and protect the security and integrity of Youporn or infrastructure. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us, in our sole discretion.

For more information on recipients of personal information, please see the section “Contact Information” below on how to contact us.

8\. Cookies and Automatic Data Collection Technologies
------------------------------------------------------

As you navigate through and interact with Youporn , we use automatic data collection technologies to collect website activity data. The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include cookies, which are small text files that are stored in your web browser or downloaded to your device when you visit Youporn . For more information on how we use cookies, please refer to our   [Cookie Notice](https://www.youporn.com/information/cookie-notice/).

9\. Your Choices About How We Process and Disclose Your Personal Information
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us.

*   You can choose not to provide us with certain personal information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of Youporn because such information may be required for you to create an account, use our products or services, participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes, communicate with our support teams, or initiate other activities on Youporn.
*   The Cookie Banner can be utilized to customize your cookie preferences. The Cookie Banner will record when you have consented to our cookies. For logged in users, we will ask for consent once a year or when we have major changes to our cookies, to ensure you stay up to date with changes to our cookies and privacy policies. For non-logged in users, your Cookie Banner selection will be kept only for the specific session. The Cookie Banner specifically controls the Functionality, Analytics, and Advertising cookies set by using Youporn. Strictly necessary cookies cannot be disabled, nor can the tool be used to block cookies on third party websites linked from Youporn. You can access the Cookie Banner anytime by clicking on the ‘Manage cookies’ option that is located at the footer of Youporn.
*   You can opt out of receiving marketing emails from us using the opt-out link provided in our emails or by changing your preferences in your account settings. You may use your account settings to delete your user contributions and audio/video information.
*   You may also delete and deactivate your account with us at any time unless required not to do so by law or by a court order. If you do so, your profile will no longer be accessible by you. If you later choose to have an account with us, you will have to sign up for a new account as none of the information you previously provided or saved within your account will have been saved.
*   Where we provide you personalised services, we may analyse the information you supply, as well as your activity on Youporn , so that we can offer a more relevant, tailored service. For instance, we could use your favourites' list to provide you with personalised content recommendations or ads. If you don’t want to receive these services, you can switch off the recommendations toggle on the “recommended” page or via the bar at the left of our page. For more information on how we use recommendations,  please [read about our recommendations](https://www.youporn.com/information/recommender/).
    
*   U.S. residents- You can learn more about the additional choices available to you under applicable state privacy laws in the “U.S. State Privacy Rights and Choices” section below. Residents of the EEA and the UK can learn more about the additional choices available to you under applicable privacy laws in the “EEA or UK Rights Related to Your Personal Information” section below.

 10. Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information
-----------------------------------------------------

Subject to local law and applicable legal requirements and exemptions, you have certain rights regarding your Personal Data.

*   **Right of access**: you have the right to receive information on the Personal Data we hold about you and how such Personal Data is used, as well as a copy of your Personal Data;
    
*   **Right to rectification**: you have the right to rectify inaccurate Personal Data concerning you;
    
*   **Right to be forgotten (for EEA, UK and Quebec residents)**: you have the right to delete/erase your Personal Data;
    
*   **Right to de-indexing (for Quebec residents):** you have the right to request that a technology-based intermediary cease disseminating Personal Information through search engines or other similar tools, subject to certain exceptions
    
*   **Right to data portability (for EEA, UK and Quebec residents)**: you have the right to receive the Personal Data provided by you in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format and to transmit this Personal Data to another controller;
    
*   **Right to object**: you have the right to object to the use of your Personal Data where such use is based on our legitimate interests or on public interests; 
    
*   **Right to restriction of processing**: you have the right in some cases, to restrict our use of your Personal Data; and
    
*   **Right to file a complaint**: you also have a right to file a complaint with your local data protection authority.

If we ask for your consent to process your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time with effect for the future. Note that, in that case, you may no longer able to use several functionalities on Youporn or access Youporn in some cases.

You can exercise your rights of access or deletion of your Personal Data by following the dedicated links in the section “_Manage Your Personal Data_” below. You can send an e-mail at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) to exercise your rights to Rectification, Object, Restriction of Processing, or to request us to help you with the process. Please note that we have one (1) month to respond to your request. 

Prior to processing an access or deletion request of your Personal Data, we will need to verify your identity and ensure your right to access or delete the information. This is an appropriate and reasonable security measure to ensure that Personal Data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it or deleted in an unauthorized way. 

Please note that unless you have created an account with us, we may not have sufficient information to identify you and therefore may not be able to respond to your request. Additionally, in some cases, to adequately verify your identity or your authorization to make the request, we may require you to provide additional information.

Note that some requests to delete certain Personal Information will require the deletion of your user account as the provision of user accounts is inextricably linked to the processing of certain Personal Information (e.g., your e-mail address). If you delete your account, your Personal Data and all account related information including, but not limited to, user profile data, sharing data and any data or content specifically associated with your account will no longer be accessible. If, after deleting your account, you wish to have an account with us in the future, you will have to sign up for a new account.

11\. U.S. State Privacy Rights and Choices
------------------------------------------

Specific U.S. states grant individuals certain rights under state privacy laws with respect to Personal Information that we collect.  If you are subject to the  U.S privacy laws, this section of the Privacy Notice contains disclosures required by law and explains rights that may be available to you. 

We share Personal Information for targeted advertising purposes but do not otherwise engage in “sales” of Personal Information as defined by state laws.  Additionally, we do not knowingly sell or share Personal Information of individuals under 18.  We do not use or disclose sensitive Personal Information, as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) for purposes that require an opt-out opportunity under the CCPA. 

We may use and disclose deidentified information to the extent permitted by applicable law.  When we use deidentified information, we maintain and use the information in deidentified form and do not attempt to reidentify it, except to check whether our deidentification processes satisfy the requirements of applicable law. 

**Your Rights**

Residents of certain states have rights with respect to the Personal Information collected by Youporn .  You may be able to exercise the following rights regarding Personal Information, subject to certain exceptions and limitations: 

*   The right to opt-out of: (i) the sharing or processing of Personal Information for targeted advertising and (ii) the sale of  Personal Information about you. Please note that if you opt out of certain practices, we may be unable to provide you with some services. 
*   The right to confirm whether we are processing Personal Information about you.
*   The right to know the categories and specific pieces of Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you; the categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information about you; our purposes for collecting, selling, or sharing Personal Information about you; the categories of Personal Information about you that we have sold or disclosed for a business purpose; and the categories of third parties to which we have sold or disclosed Personal Information. 
*   For Minnesota and Oregon residents, a list of the specific third parties to which we have disclosed Personal Information. 
*   The right to receive a portable and readily usable copy of the Personal Information we have collected about you, to the extent feasible. 
*   The right to correct inaccuracies in the Personal Information we have collected about you.
*   The right to request that we delete certain Personal Information we collected about you. 
*   Depending on your state law, you can: 
    *   Opt-out of our processing of certain “sensitive” information; or 
    *   Withdraw consent for such processing if you previously gave it. 
*   Not be subjected to discrimination for the exercise of these rights. We will not deny residents the use of our service, neither will we provide a different level or quality of services for exercising any of their state privacy rights, unless as permitted under the applicable state law.

Additionally, if you have submitted a request that we have not reasonably fulfilled, you may contact us to appeal our decision by sending an email with the subject line “Appeal” to [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com) .

If you would like to exercise your rights, please use the buttons at the bottom of this page or email us at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com)  with the email subject line “U.S. Privacy Rights Request”.

In either case we may need to request the following information to verify your identity and enable us to locate your information in our systems: your username and email address that you used to create an account with us, as well as any other information which we may reasonably request for us to verify your identity. For Registered Users, we may require you verify that you have access to your account and/or email account that you used to register with us.

You can designate an agent to make a request by executing a notarized power of attorney to have that person act on your behalf and providing that person with the information listed above that allows us to verify your identity and locate your information. Alternatively, you will need to directly confirm your identity with us using the methods described above, sign an authorization for the agent to act on your behalf and provide us with confirmation that you have done so.  We will require the agent to provide us with proof that you have authorized the agent to make requests on your behalf prior to responding to requests from the agent.

12\. Biometric Information
--------------------------

We rely on third-party service providers to verify your identity, age, and the authenticity of the identification documents you provide using facial recognition technology. Facial recognition technology creates a mathematical representation of your facial features from the live scan of your face, your selfie, and the government-issued ID you submit or previously submitted to us. Face recognition data is collected by and remains with our third-party providers. We do not process face recognition data.

When applicable, your biometric information may be processed to:

*   verify you are a real, live person and to prevent the use of methods which would allow a user to identify as someone else;
    
*   to match your selfie with your government-issued ID you submit or previously submitted to us to make sure that nobody is impersonating you;
    
*   to help confirm your age. 

You will be asked to provide your consent to biometric information processing which you may withdraw at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any collection, use, processing, or disclosure that occurred prior to the withdrawal. We invite you to consult our third-party service providers’ privacy notices and terms and conditions.   

13\. Notice to Law Enforcement
------------------------------

The following information serves as a guideline for law enforcement officials seeking disclosure of records. You may serve us a valid court order, subpoena, search warrant or equivalent legal or official administrative document by respecting the following conditions:

1.  The document(s) is uploaded, and all required fields have been filed out adequately on our platform for Legal Service Process located at: [https://legalservice.aylo.com/legal/datarequest](https://legalservice.aylo.com/legal/datarequest);
    
2.  The document(s) you are serving is correctly issued to Aylo Freesites Ltd by a valid Court of Law or equivalent legal or administrative authority to us;
    
3.  The document(s) is also sent by mail at the following address: 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540.

We reserve the right to refuse online service through Youporn, namely in cases where the above requirements are not met and require formal legal service at the above address. In such an event, you will be notified. We may raise or waive any legal objection or right available, in our sole discretion.

14\. Transfers of Your Personal Information to Other Countries
--------------------------------------------------------------

We may share the information we collect globally, across our corporate group and with our service providers and other third parties. Transfers are necessary for a variety of reasons, including our operation and provision of the services stated in our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.youporn.com/info/terms) and this Privacy Notice to fix, analyse, and improve our Website, products and services. 

**For EEA and UK residents:** Whenever we transfer Personal Information to countries outside the EEA, the UK and other regions with comprehensive data protection laws, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy Notice, as permitted by the applicable laws and based on appropriate mechanisms.

Where applicable, we rely on decisions of the European Commission, known as “adequacy decisions,” recognizing that certain countries offer a level of protection to Personal Data that is essentially equivalent to the EEA and/or the UK. 

In other situations, where transferring Personal Data to countries outside the EEA and/or the UK that do not benefit from an “adequacy decision”, we rely on standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission (and the equivalent standard contractual clauses for the UK, where appropriate) or on derogations provided for under the applicable law to transfer information to a third country.

**For the rest of the world:** Any transfer of Personal Information outside of your country of residence will be carried out in accordance with the requirements applicable in your country of residence.

For more information or to obtain a copy of our standard contractual clauses, please see the section “Contact Information” below on how to contact us.

15\. Retention of Personal Information
--------------------------------------

In general, we will keep your Personal Data for as long as it is needed for the provision of our services, subject to the locally applicable statutory period of retention.

In particular, where applicable, we will only retain your Personal Information for as long as your account is active, or for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we processed it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.

To determine the appropriate retention period for Personal Data, we consider several factors, including what Personal Data we are processing, the risk of harm from any unauthorized disclosure, why we are processing your Personal Data and whether we can achieve this outcome by another means without having to process it.

Where we no longer need to process your Personal Information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice, we will delete your Personal Information from our systems. 

For more information on data retention periods, please see the section “_Contact Information_” below on how to contact us. 

Where permissible, we will also delete your Personal Information upon your request as explained in the section _“Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information” and “U.S. State Privacy Rights and Choices” sections of this Privacy Notice_.

For more information on data retention periods, please contact us by using the information in the Section _"Contact Information"_ below.

Where permissible, we will also delete your personal information upon your request as explained in the section _"Your Rights Related to Your Personal Information"_.

16\. Third-Party Links and Sites
--------------------------------

Youpornmay provide links to third-party websites or apps.  If you click on a link to a third-party website, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This Privacy Notice does not apply to the privacy practices of these websites. Read the Privacy Notice of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third-party practices.

Youporn also includes integrated social media tools or “plug-ins,” such as social networking tools offered by third parties.  If you use these tools to share Personal Information or you otherwise interact with these features on the Service, those companies may collect information about you and may use and share such information in accordance with your account settings, including by sharing such information with the general public. 

Your interactions with third-party companies and your use of their features are governed by the privacy notices of the companies that provide those features. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy notices of any accounts you create and use. 

17\. Changes to Our Privacy Notice
----------------------------------

We keep our Privacy Notice under regular review. The scope is to address any new legal requirements, technical developments or add more clarifications where needed. 

Although we may attempt to notify you when major changes are made to this Privacy Notice, you are expected to periodically review the most up-to-date version found at this location, so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you. If we change anything in our Privacy Notice, the date of change will be reflected in the “Last Modified” date mentioned after the header of this Privacy Notice. 

18\. Contact Information
------------------------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our information-handling practices, please contact us at [support@youporn.com](mailto:support@youporn.com).

You may also contact us at 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road, Block 1 Dali Industrial Zone, Cyprus 2540, Phone: +357 22662 320, Fax: +357 22343 282.

Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at the following email address: [dpo@youporn.com](mailto:dpo@youporn.com).

19\. Manage My Data
-------------------

You may request a copy of Personal Data about you or request the deletion of  Personal Data about you via the links below. Please note that the below website is governed by the present Privacy Notice.  

_Note: AdBlocker add-ons interfere with the Manage My Data system. Please disable them._
